Malleable Iron Fittings Company Records 1982.0004
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series II: Records, undated, 1878-1939
  - Treasurer's Correspondence, undated (Box 17)
  - Thatcher Correspondence, undated (Box 18)
  - Contracts, undated (Box 19)
  - Production Records, undated (Box 20)
  - Inspection Time Sheets, undated (Box 21)
  - Production Records and Information, undated (Box 22)
  - Executive Files, undated (Box 23, Box 24, Box 25)
  - Bills
    - 1871-1872, 1882 (Box 26)
    - 1878 (Box 27)
    - 1879 (Box 28)
    - 1884 (Box 29)
    - 1884-1886 (Box 30)
    - 1885 (Box 31)
    - 1886-1891 (Box 32)
    - 1887-1889 (Box 33)
    - 1888 (Box 34)
    - 1888 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence to and from T. F. Hammer, 1898-1899, 1928-1933 (Box 36)
  - Incoming correspondence, 1891-1894, 1900-1901 (Box 37)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1892, 1989, 1928 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence from suppliers and other businesses, 1902, 1920-1927, 1934-1939 (Box 39)
  - Correspondence with Hammer Company, 1894-1901 (Box 40)